Register of the Alfred M. Lilienthal papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- PHOTOGRAPHS, 1945-1984 (Photo file)
  - 3 prints of AML at the UN with UAE Ambassador Saif Ghorbash, Qatar Ambassador Jassim Jamal (Envelope FO)
  - 1 print depicting AML at the UN with the Saudi consul general (Envelope FP)
  - 1 print of AML with Saudi Oil Minister Ahmad Zaki Yamani (Envelope FQ)
  - 3 prints of AML in Egypt at night clubs and at the Auberge des Pyramides (Envelope FR)
  - 3 prints and 1 negative of AML in Kuwait dancing at the home of businessman Bader Mulla, and being interviewed by Kabussi of Al Qabas (Envelope FS)
  - 3 prints of AML in Lebanon at party honoring him (Envelope FT)
  - 11 prints of unidentified people and 1 one of AML with Algerian ambassador and Mrs. Benhima (Envelope FU)
  - 29 prints depicting Egypt (Envelope FV)
  - 15 prints depicting Israel (Envelope FW)
  - 4 prints depicting Kuwait (Envelope FX)
  - 10 prints depicting Lebanon and Jordan, including the Middle East shelf at the American University of Beirut Library (Envelope FY)
  - 9 prints depicting various pro-Israel demonstrations in New York City (Envelope FZ)
  - 4 prints depicting Saudi Arabia, including 1 of a convicted Saudi with hand severed (Envelope GA)
  - 6 prints depicting Syria (Envelope GB)
  - 3 prints depicting the Tunisian Trade and Tourist Office in New York City (Envelope GC)
  - 1 print depicting a scene from the film Lawrence of Arabia (Envelope GD)
  - 8 prints depicting Ingrid Bergman in the film Golda (Envelope GE)
  - 19 prints depicting Anthony Quinn and others in the film Mohammad, Messenger of God (Envelope GF)
  - 4 negatives and 42 strips of negative (Envelope GG)
- INCREMENTAL MATERIALS (Boxes 154-272)
  This addition to the collection has not yet been described. Please let the Hoover Institution Archives know if you would like to see this material described.